Guide to the Lewis L. Delafield, Eugene D. Hawkins and Affiliated Attorneys Records circa 1856-1921 (bulk, 1880s-1910) MS 157
New-York Historical Society
- Series III. Boxes labeled H-D (Hawkins-Delafield), circa 1853-1924 (bulk 1880s-1910)
  - H-D Bundles #268, 275-285, circa 1902-1904 (Offsite-box 73)
    278) Agreements between Armedia S. Clark, Jennie P. Childs and George A. Clark, ca. 1902.
    279) Claim of Sara L. Miller on Edward L. Bonner estate, ca. 1902.
    280) Appraisal of property of Georgiana Parsons, deceased, ca. 1904.
    281) Agreement between Fred A. Verdon and Detrick & Harvey Machine Company, ca. 1903.
    282) Russell Bellamy v. Henry W. Warner, ca. 1903.
    283) Arthur Tooth v. J. Eastman Chase, ca. 1903.
  - H-D Bundles #288-290 (part), circa 1880-1901 (Offsite-box 74)
    288) Emily Scott property matter, ca. 1900.
    289) Anna E. Marks v. Germania Savings Bank of New Orleans, ca. 1901. Also, Anna Marks v. Theodore H. Price, William G. McCormick, Ralph M. Stuart-Wortley (firm of Price, McCormick & Co), ca. 1898-1900.
    290) #290 relates to the Pickhardt estate and related matters. In the original H-D boxes, the documents ranged across several boxes. This box holds Wilhelm Pickhardt-related invoices, ca. 1895-96, and correspondence, etc, mostly it seems re: Schroon Lake matters (some re: Leland House), ca. 1880s.
  - H-D Bundles #290 (continued), circa 1890s-1908 (Offsite-box 75)
    #290 relates to the Pickhardt estate and related matters. In the original H-D boxes, the documents ranged across several boxes. This box holds Wilhelm Pickhardt estate papers, ca. 1890s-1902, and Sydney Beresford Pickhardt estate, and other Pickhardts estate and other matters, ca. 1890s-1908.
  - H-D Bundles #290 (continued), circa 1880s-1902 (Offsite-box 76)
    #290 relates to the Pickhardt estate and related matters. In the original H-D boxes, the documents ranged across several boxes. This box holds the matter of the Pickhardt estate re: Warren County property, ca. 1880s; 2 letterpress copybooks of Wilhelm Pickhardt and Adolf Kuttroff, 1880s; and Pickhardt estate accounting (Beresford Pickhardt executor): Checkbook stubs, 1890s-1902.
  - H-D Bundles #290 (continued), circa 1880s (Offsite-box 77)
    #290 relates to the Pickhardt estate and related matters. In the original H-D boxes, the documents ranged across several boxes. This box holds Wilhelm Pickhardt correspondence, bills, cancelled checks, receipts, patents, agreements, accounting journal (in German), etc, re: Schroon Lake building, Leland House, and other matters, ca 1880s.
  - H-D Bundles #291-296, circa 1898-1900 (Offsite-box 78)
    291) Windsor Company (Jersey City) mortgage to Howard H. Williams and other agreements, ca. 1899-1904.
    293) Mine & Smelter Supply Company and George Crocker matter, ca. 1898.
    294) Estate of Sarah A. Van Nostrand (settlement of account of executors Edward N. Crane and Charles E. Wilson; appraisal, etc.), ca. 1900.
    295) Various papers re: Emma Crocker contracts for 1 East 64th Street, New York City (Sprague Electric Company; John Tucker; Zimdars & Hunt; William H. Jackson & Co.), ca. 1898.
    296) Envelopes of various matters, most or all of which appear related to Price, McCormick & Co. (Theodore H. Price et al), ca. 1898.
  - H-D Bundles #297-299, circa 1897-1904 (Offsite-box 79)
    297) Loose mix of what appears to be multiple matters: George Crocker matter re: Price, McCormick & Co.; Abbott-Duson Canal (W.W. Duson & Bro., Crowley, LA) and other canal matters in Louisiana; agreements between George Crocker and Thomas W. Pearsall and Everett P. Wheeler and others; U.S. Flour Milling Company matters; Hunts Point property purchase by Crocker from the Spofford estate; all ca. 1897-1904.
    298) Another loose mix which appears to be mostly or entirely George Crocker matters.
    299) Title abstract and other property matters re:Charles M. Darling, Alice Darling, and Elmer A. Darling in Hohokus, Bergen County, New Jersey, ca. 1901.
  - H-D Bundles #300-313, 315-319, circa 1897-1904 (Offsite-box 80)
    300) Pickhardt estate re: sale of lands in Warren & Essex Counties.
    301) Gold Run Gravels, Ltd v. Joseph D. Redding, J.E. Doolittle and E.A. Wiltsee; also Alabama Gold Mining Company v. Redding matter, Superior Court of San Francisco, ca. 1901-02.
    302?) Various loose documents, ca. 1904.
    303) Settlement of accounts of George Nixon and Winthrop McKim, executors of Mary J. Winthrop estate, ca. 1904.
    304) [Small bundle with few documents, not identified by archivist]
    305) Sodekson v. Anderson (few documents).
    307) [Small bundle with few documents, not identified by archivist]
    308) Swears & Wells v. Havemeyer, ca. 1903.
    309) Appears to be various matters, at least some re: George Crocker, ca. 1901.
    310) William W. Sharp and Charles S. Bryan v. Ozro W. Clapp and Dwight O. Clapp (Clapp & Co.), ca. 1897.
    311) Appears to relate to various personal matters of Eugene Hawkins, including his work as executor of Dexter A. Hawkins estate, ca. 1900-03.
    312) James G. Blaine v. Edward R. Thomas et al, ca. 1904.
    313) Thomas C. Higgins v. Gertrude S. Sharp (a/k/a Gertrude S. Higgins).
    315-19) Various loose bundles with mixed-up content on miscellaneous matters.
  - H-D Bundles #314, 320-334, circa 1899-1905 (Offsite-box 81)
    314) National Coke & Gas Company matters, ca. 1901-02.
    320) Fred W. Arnold et al v. Merchants Insurance Company in Providence, ca. 1899.
    321) Harold G. Henderson will.
    322) James C. Colgate v. Bear Lithia(?) Springs Company.
    323) Armedia S. Clark v. Joseph John Byers.
    324) Application of Cornelia A. Kennedy, trustee under will of Augustus T. Voorhees and Robert C. Kennedy on behalf of infant Marguerite Kennedy to sell real estate on Marguerite's behalf, ca. 1905.
    325) [Small bundle with few documents, not identified by archivist]
    326) Matter of Samuel D. Davis & Co. bankruptcy, ca. 1903.
    327) [Small bundle with few documents, not identified by archivist]
    328) Application of Rosa Stahle for payment re: estate of Jacob G. Stahle, ca.1905.
    329) Margaret and Nelson C. Thrall property agreement with George Crocker, ca. 1905.
    330) [Small bundle with few documents, not identified by archivist]
    331) Agreement between Frederick Robitscher and David A. and Maria M. Clarkson, ca. 1904.
    332) American Peroxide and Chemical Company matters, ca, 1905.
    333) Metropolitan Finance Company stock matter.
    334) Agreements for work for Warner M. Leeds at 11 East 65th Street, including specifications for interior finish, ca. 1905.
  - H-D Bundles #335-352, circa 1853-1906 (Offsite-box 82)
    335) Agreements for work for Warner M. Leeds at 11 East 65th Street, ca. 1905.
    336) Sale by Charles A. Childs of lands, ca. 1905.
    338) John Donaldson v. Metropolitan Elevated Railroad Company, ca. 1902.
    339) Tide Water Building Company re: Kurzror (few documents).
    342) Sarah A. Meeks as executrix of Albert V. Meeks re: agreement with J. Langdon Erving and related, ca. 1906.
    343) Mary A. Tuttle agreement with Julius Wile, Alfons Wile, Ernest S. Blum and Irwin Wile, ca. 1905.
    344) Title abstract for John Jewett and Jacob Hess re: land at Hunts Point, Westchester County, ca. 1853.
    345) Julia M. Phyfe as executrix of James D. Phyfe estate et al v. Metropolitan Elevated Railroad Company and Manhattan Railway Company, ca. 1898.
    346) Charles A. Childs and Augusta D. Childs agreement with Mutual Life Insurance Company of New York, ca. 1906.
    347) Sarah Miller v. Charles C. Miller and Mercantile Safe Deposit Company, ca. 1905.
    348) Rachael Lichtenstein v. New York and Harlem Railroad Company and New York Central and Hudson River Railroad Company, ca. 1905.
    349) Mary M. Morrison agreement with Metropolitan Safe Deposit Company and International Steam Pump Company, ca. 1906.
    350) Elizabeth S. Melville agreement with Metropolitan Safe Deposit Company, ca. 1906.
    351) [Small bundle with few documents, not identified by archivist]
    352) Appears to relate to the matter of fundraising for a proposed Alumni Hall at Phillips' Exeter Academy, ca. 1900-05.
  - H-D Bundles #353-387, circa 1894-1906 (Offsite-box 83)
    353) Sarah A. Meeks as executrix of Albert V. Meeks estate matter, ca. 1904-06.
    354) Tide Water Building Company re: Lewkowitz.
    355) Crowley Oil & M. [Mining?] Company re: claims of Louis Kaufman & S.J. & S. Co.
    356) Building contracts between Henry W. Warner and William Craft for a house at Mattinacock, Nassau County, ca. 1905.
    358) Frank P. Bennett & Co., Inc. matters.
    359) People v. Rutherford (few documents).
    363) Charles E. Schnall v. George W. Perkins, ca. 1907.
    364) Van Norden Trust Company as assignee of James Clarke and Hudson Clarke.
    366) Frank B. Walker v. Van Kirkman.
    368) The Exchanges Publishing Company v. The Standard Chemical Company, ca. 1894.
    369) Application of Talbot J. Taylor and James B. Taylor, judgement creditors, for examination of Samuel T. Hubbard, et al, ca. 1903.
    370) Phillips' Exeter building matter, ca. 1906.
    371) Matter re: Flagg (estate of Josiah Dodge).
    372) Matter of burial of Francis P. Vidal, ca. 1907.
    373) Clock Cash Register Co. Ltd. agreememt with M. Gustine Rieser, ca. 1907.
    374) Ivey v. Townsend.
    376) Statement of intent to do business by M.& H. Clarkson, ca. 1907.
    378) [Small bundle with few documents, not identified by archivist].
    379) E.W. Brewer assignment of mortgage on premises at Olinsville.
    380) M.S. Godfrey v. Toppan Manufacturing Company.
    381) Ward v. Gwathway et al.
    382) Eastern Trust Company matter.
    383) Robert C. Nichols matter (few documents).
    384) Matter of Samuel and Helen H. Hunt, bankruptcy, ca. 1901.
    385) Miles H. Williams v. Charles A. Baldwin Company, ca. 1899.
    386) [Small bundle with few documents, not identified by archivist].
    387) Matter of Harry K. Thaw.
  - H-D Bundles #389-394, 396-397, circa 1873-1907 (Offsite-box 84)
    389) Frank A. Otis, trustee under estate of Uriah J. Smith, v. Henry Chauncey et al, ca. 1902.
    390) Manila Navigation Company matters with E.J. Callan and others, ca. 1907.
    391) Waldo Grant Morse, executor of Ruby Tilden Paine estate, v. Samuel J. Tilden, Jr et al, ca. 1901.
    392) Matter of de la Garza (few documents).
    393) American Cigar Company v. United States; G. Falk & Brother v. United States.
    394) Joseph Hughes v. New York Elevated Railroad Company, Manhattan Railway Company, et al, ca. 1893-1905.
    396) John E. Bullwinkel v. Henry Geerken et al, ca. 1902.
    397) Title abstract to George L. Felt for 51 Cliff St, New York City.
    There are also other miscellaneous loose items here that were in the original box holding bundles part of 395 and 396-397. These various items include, but may not be limited to: William G. McCrea v. Mutual Bank, ca. 1904; George Ahrens v. Cornelia Ahrens et al, ca. 1901; Rufus Delafield deed to Nathaniel Prime and Edward Prime Jr, 1873; trustees of Sailors' Snug Harbor in the City of New York v. Henry E. Ficken, ca. 1901; William Bard will.
  - H-D Bundles #395, circa 1905 (Offsite-box 85)
    This entire box holds one matter: 395) Thomas P. Wickes v. Edward S. Hatch, Frank M. Clute, J. Stuart Tompkins, and George C. Lay, ca. 1905.
  - H-D Bundles #398-402, circa 1901-1916 (Offsite-box 86)
    398) William Manger et al v. Victor Hugo Kimmelmann et al, Kings County, ca. 1903.
    399) John D. Leary v. New York Life Insurance Company, et al, Saratoga County, ca. 1906.
    400) New York State Bar Association annual meeting, 1908.
    401) Rosenthal matter (few documents).
    402) Ruby Tilden Paine estate matters, including accounts of Willis S. Paine, administrator, ca. 1901.
    Also a set of envelopes with documents that also appear to be numbered as 400: Settlement of estate of Isaac C. Kendall, and related matters, ca. 1916.
  - H-D Bundles #403-439, circa 1888-1907 (Offsite-box 87)
    403) Sarah A. O'Reilly, Hugh O'Reilly, Sarah M. O'Reilly et al v. Manhattan Railway Company, ca. 1895-1903.
    404) Emily P. Delafield (landlord) v. Edward Cassidy (tenant), ca. 1899.
    405) Emily P. Delafield (landlord) v. Leonard Hyams (tenant), et al, ca. 1906.
    407) Matter involving L.G. Harris and Nova Scotia coal mines, Debert coal field, and Colchester Coal & Railway Co. Ltd, ca. 1903.
    408) Blank stationery for Lowe Coke and Gas Securities Company, New York.
    409) Bernard H. Foss v. New York Elevated Railroad Company, Manhattan Railway Company, Emigrant Savings Bank, and Christian Dohm, ca. 1898-1902.
    410) Cyrus D. Foss, George W. Robertson and Joseph Dixon (executors of James Robertson estate) v. Ravenswood Art Glass Works, New Central Coal Company, et al, Queens County, ca. 1899.
    411) New Central Coal Company v. Ravenswood Art Glass Works, ca. 1895.
    412) Louise O. Hunter (executrix of Jacob Hunter estate) v. New York Elevated Railroad Company and Manhattan Railway Company, ca. 1898.
    414) Detrick & Harvey Machine Company (of Baltimore), collection claims against H.A. Fergusson and against Driggs, Seabury Gun & Ammunition Company, ca. 1900.
    417) Matter re: Policyholders' Protective Association of the Mutual Life Insurance Company of New York, ca. 1906.
    418) Warner & Co., assignment by A.H. Herreboudt of account in bank.
    419) Nathaniel Gordon matter (few documents).
    421) Wilson Godfrey estate matters, ca. 1907.
    422) Bon Air Coal & Iron Company v. Arthur G. Sherman (few documents).
    423) Route change of new Elm Street and Pearl Street, and application of Elise Boyd for damages caused by change of grade, ca. 1905.
    432) Purchase by Howard Clarkson of property at Clermont near Tivoli, Columbia County, New York, and related matters, ca. 1904.
    436) Union League Club (Manhattan) building, staff, etc. matters directed to Eugene Hawkins as Chairman of the Club's House Committee, ca. 1901.
    437) Printed booklet with certificate of incorporation for Lowe Coke and Gas Securities Company.
    438) Joseph S. Bryce v. Louisville, New Albany & Chicago Railway Company and other matters related to that railroad, ca. 1888-1890s.
    439B) Frank Abbott estate matters, ca. 1897-1899.
  - H-D Bundles #440-447, circa 1894-1907 (Offsite-box 88)
    440) Bank of Long Island v. John Alvin Young (typescript of testimony), ca. 1907.
    441) James J. Ward v. Metropolitan Elevated Railroad Company, Manhattan Railway Company, et al, ca. 1894-95.
    442) Farmers' Loan & Trust Company v. Josiah H. Barker, receiver for Hotel Brunswick Company, ca. 1896.
    443) Milk company corporate matters (Pure Milk Company; Century Milk Company), ca. 1899.
    A second bundle numbered 443 holds correspondence re: Zwoyer Fuel Company, ca. 1901.
    445) This is a small bundle with what seems a mix of things, including more documents re: Louisville, New Albany & Chicago Railway Company, ca. 1890s-1903.
    446) Samuel M. Burbank transfer tax matter (few documents).
    447) Eugene D. Hawkins horse show prize certificate.
    447A) G. Amsinck et al v. W. Loaiza & Company et al; and F. Muller et al v. W. Loaiza & Company et al (few documents).
  - H-D Bundles #448-453, 456-463, circa 1890-1908 (Offsite-box 89)
    448) Robert Sturgis will and estate matters, ca. 1900 (Marion Sturgis, executrix).
    448A) Susan B. Sturgis (Philadelphia) will and estate, ca. 1900.
    449A) Application of Caleb A. Burbank for admission to the Bar and many other papers (cancelled checks, etc) re: Burbank, ca. 1905.
    449B) Loose papers on various matters that appears to be all related to Caleb A. Burbank issues, ca. 1900-05.
    450) Bernhard Schwerin v. Metropolitan Elevated Railroad Company, Manhattan Railway Company, et al, ca. 1891.
    451) Correspondence re: Eugene Hawkins's activities on the Executive Committee of the Bar Association, ca. 1908.
    452) Settlement of accounts of Edward L. Norton and Theophilus Gilman as administrators of George F. Gilman estate, ca. 1908.
    453) Hugh E. O'Reilly v. Interborough Rapid Transit Company and Manhattan Railway Company, ca. 1907-08.
    456) City of New York v. Emily P. Delafield (few documents).
    457) Isaac Whiting re: Daly-Whiting Mining (few documents).
    458) Helen Florence Lucas v. Mary Cleveland, ca. 1908.
    462) Warner M. Leeds v. Ida G. Whitney re: loan.
    463) Warner M. Leeds re: Bar Harbor title (few documents).
  - H-D Bundles #454, 464-466, circa 1893-1903 (Offsite-box 90)
    454 and 454A) Settlement of accounts of Lucy Chauncey, executrix of Henry Chauncey Jr estate, ca. 1899-1902.
    464) Settlement of accounts of Edwin B. Meeks, executor of Joseph W. Meeks estate, Suffolk County, ca. 1893.
    465) Frank Martinek v. Charles A. Childs (few documents).
    466) Various matters with a few documents each, including Louisville, New Albany & Chicago Railway Company; estate of Sarah A. Van Nostrand; and some others, ca. 1893-1903.
  - H-D Bundles #467-483, circa 1897-1912 (Offsite-box 91)
    467) Application of Sarah Elizabeth Flagg for payment of an award for parcels 248 and 268 made to unknown owners in the matter of opening the Grand Boulevard and Concourse from East 161st Street to Mosholu Parkway, ca. 1897.
    468) Agreements/property sale: Robert W. Tailer to Minnie Flagg, ca. 1912.
    469) Charles B. Harris v. Silas I. Atwater re: Skaguay Terminal Company (Washington State), ca. 1898-1904.
    471) Robert Easton Irwin v. Acme Soap Company (bankrupt), ca. 1899.
    472) Dissolution of the American Peroxide & Chemical Company.
    473) Morris K. Jesup re: Guaranty Trust Company of New York v. Troy Steel Company, ca. 1902.
    473A) Benjamin B. Hamlin Jr (as minority stockholder of American Peroxide & Chemical Company) v. George Crocker et al, ca. 1906.
    474) Nesmith v. Walter W. Lawson (few documents).
    475) Matter of re-nomination of Charles H. Beckett as surrogate.
    476) Jennie P. Childs will, ca. 1908.
    477) Urania C. Welling v. Alrick H. Man, ca. 1905.
    478) Diary of legal matters worked on daily. Possibly Eugene Hawkins activities only, but not clear. Appears to be 1907-08.
    480) Agreements involving Lynford M. Dickinson, Garetta M. Dickinson, Samuel C. Henning, et al, ca. 1908.
    482) Edward L. Kalbfleisch Jr v. American Peroxide & Chemical Company, ca. 1906.
    483) Settlement of accounts of Gamaliel C. St. John, executor of Wallace C. Andrews estate, ca. 1904.
  - H-D Bundles #484-493, 495-499, circa 1894-1909 (Offsite-box 92)
    484) Theodore H. Price et al (firm of Price, McCormick & Co) v. Theodore Werner, ca. 1898.
    485) Application of Thomas Seton Jevons for admission to the New York Bar.
    486) George Crocker matters.
    487) Gladys Phipps v. R. Livingston Beeckman, Nassau County, and other agreements that relate to George Crocker and others, ca. 1908-09.
    489) Application for dissolution of the British American Insurance Company, ca. 1908.
    Also loose miscellaneous documents (488?) with at least some relating to George Crocker.
    490) Theodore Haebler v. Samuel T. Hubbard et al, ca. 1900.
    492) Claims of Clarence C. Howard against Louis A. Wagner, executor of Trelove E. O'Brien estate.
    493) Title abstract for Margaret P. Francioli to premises on 117th and 118th streets, New York City.
    495) Augusta D. Childs application for reduction of taxes on 26 East 56th Street.
    495A) Manhattan Granite Company matters, ca. 1905.
    496) Frank Kiernan and Ida M. Kiernan v. Toppan Manufacturing Company, ca. 1896.
    497) Findlay, Fort Wayne and Western Railway Company matters, ca. 1894.
    498) Hudson Realty Company agreement with Century Bank of New York City, ca. 1905.
    499) "Memorandum in opposition to a bill [880] authorizing the re-conveyance of certain lands taken for the extension of the New York and Brooklyn Bridge." Lewis Delafield working as attorney for "certain property owners," ca. 1901.
  - H-D Bundles #494, 500-502, circa 1901-1909 (Offsite-box 93)
    494, 494A) Bank of Long Island v. John Alvin Young, Queens County, ca. 1900-09. Also includes papers re: notes of W.R. Cole & Co endorsed by National Cooperage Company and discounted by Bank of Jamaica, ca. 1901-02, that relate to Young's case.
    500) Catherine L. Meeks, executrix of Joseph W. Meeks Jr estate v. Edwin B. Meeks as executor of Joseph W. Meeks Sr estate, et al, Kings County, ca. 1903.
    501) Matter re: Mary Ann Searle estate, ca. 1909.
    502) Howard Willets v. Henry W. Poor et al, ca. 1909.
  - H-D Bundles #503-526, circa 1897-1909 (Offsite-box 94)
    503) Anna M. Arrowsmith v. J. Hood Wright Memorial Hospital, ca. 1902.
    505) Agreements re: Armedia S. Clark, Black Leaf Land & Cattle Company (Montana) and First National Bank of Great Falls, ca. 1905.
    508) Matter of J.J. Frank, Mashbir & Cukor, ca. 1909 (few documents).
    509) George Crocker v. Nelson C. Thrall re: Brookhill Land Company.
    510) Estate of Leonard J. Wyette (few documents).
    511) Estate of Moses Hawkins (Henry Hawkins, administrator).
    514) Jacobs v. Mayer (few documents).
    515) Theodore H. Price, William G. McCormick, Ralph M. Stuart-Wortley (firm of Price, McCormick & Co) v. William E. B. Matheson, ca. 1897.
    518) John T. Sproul (trustee) v. Hutchison Acoustic Company, ca. 1909.
    519) Caleb A. Burbank re: bond of Mary L. Burbank as guardian of Grace Burbank.
    520) Julia F. Baldwin and Cordelia A. Ogden (trustees under will of Susan Baldwin) v. William H. Baldwin et al, ca. 1901.
    522) Estate of Moses Hawkins (few documents).
    523) Caleb A. Burbank re: miscellaneous matters (few documents).
    524) Settlement of account of Edward L. Norton and Theophilus Gilman as administrators of George F. Gilman estate, ca. 1908.
    525) New York State Bar Association matter re: nominations etc.
    526) Town of Hempstead v. Queens Borough Gas and Electric Company, Nassau County, ca. 1905.
  - H-D Bundles #527-530, 533-536, 539, circa 1895-1909 (Offsite-box 95)
    527) Kate E. Price matter re: premises at Arverne-by-the-Sea, Queens County, ca. 1905.
    528) Proposed subscriptions for the Charles William Eliot Fund of the Harvard Club, ca. 1909.
    529) Johanna Kalish et al (executors of Joseph Kalish estate) v. Luke Higgins and Elizabeth Higgins, ca. 1901.
    530) James M. Hartshorne et al (executor of Sarah L. Hartshorne estate) v. New York Elevated Railroad Company and Manhattan Railway Company, ca. 1895-1902.
    533) Guion Thompson and Huntington W. Merchant re: Thompson Safety Appliance Company, ca. 1902.
    534) Jennie P. Childs re: Childs will and Tarrytown property, ca. 1907.
    535) Thomas W. Fleming v. Edward V. d'Invilliers and Malcolm Baxter Jr, ca. 1901.
    536) Roger Wolcott estate (appraisal, etc.), ca. 1906.
    539) Specimen Tree Transplanting and Construction Company agreements and corporate matters, ca. 1906.
  - H-D Bundles #532, 538, circa 1904-1908 (Offsite-box 96)
    532, 532A) Frances J. Storms and Alfred Storms v. New York Elevated Railroad Company and Manhattan Railway Company, ca. 1897-1904.
    538) Various matters concerning Leonard J. Wyeth 3rd (infant) including application for appointment of special guardian, application to sell Wyeth's real estate, etc. Some matters concerning Leonard J. Wyeth, Jr. ca. 1904-08.
  - H-D Bundles #540-548, circa 1901-1907 (Offsite-box 97)
    540) Examination as to solvency of Fidelity and Deposit Company of Maryland, ca. 1907.
    541) Property contracts re: Henry G. Trevor, City Real Estate Company, and others, ca. 1906.
    542) Bank of Long Island v. National Cooperage Company and William R. Cole, ca. 1903.
    543) People of State of New York ex rel Citizens Lighting Company v. Thomas L. Feitner et al as Commissioners of Taxes and Assessments for New York City, ca. 1903.